,Linked Page,Directory Page,University,Entity,Maybe Uni
Andrew Abbott,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/andrew-abbott,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/andrew-abbott,University of Chicago,"[[('University of Chicago', 'ORG')]]",University of Chicago
Eman Abdelhadi,https://humdev.uchicago.edu/directory/eman-abdelhadi,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/eman-abdelhadi,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Michael E. Albertus,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/michael-albertus,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/michael-e-albertus,D Stanford,"[[('Stanford', 'ORG')]]",Stanford
Fredrik Albritton Jonsson,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/fredrik-albritton-jonsson,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/fredrik-albritton-jonsson,University of Chicago,"[[('University of Chicago', 'ORG')]]",University of Chicago
Guy S. Alitto,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/guy-salvatore-alitto,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/guy-s-alitto,Harvard University,"[[('Harvard University', 'ORG')]]",Harvard University
Fernando Alvarez,https://economics.uchicago.edu/directory/fernando-alvarez,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/fernando-alvarez,University of Minnesota,"[[('University of Minnesota', 'ORG')]]",University of Minnesota
Clifford  Ando,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/clifford-ando,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/clifford-ando,University of Michigan,"[[('University of Michigan', 'ORG')]]",University of Michigan
Sneha  Annavarapu,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/content/postdoctoral-researchers,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/sneha-annavarapu,"Sneha Annavarapu's research interests include gender, globalization, qualitative methodology, social change, social theory, and urban sociology. She received her PhD in Sociology from the University of Chicago in 2020.","[[(""Sneha Annavarapu's"", 'PERSON')], [('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]]",the University of Chicago
Luc Anselin,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/luc-anselin,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/luc-anselin,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Brett Baker,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/brett-baker,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Chaevia Clendinen,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/chaevia-clendinen,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Paul Fatula,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/paul-fatula,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Jacqueline Hill,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/jacqueline-hill,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Cathy Mican,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/cathy-mican,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Kelly Therese Pollock,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/kelly-therese-pollock,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Lindsey Weglarz,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/lindsey-weglarz,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Joshua Beck,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/joshua-beck,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Katie Kaftanich,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/katie-kaftanich,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Rohit Rijhsinghani,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/rohit-rijhsinghani,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Yasmin Omer,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/yasmin-omer,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Elizabeth Braun Rush,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/elizabeth-braun-rush,Cornell University,"[[('Cornell University', 'ORG')]]",Cornell University
Jennifer Cole,https://humdev.uchicago.edu/directory/jennifer-cole,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/jennifer-cole,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Andreas Glaeser,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/andreas-glaeser,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/andreas-glaeser,Harvard University,"[[('Harvard University', 'ORG')]]",Harvard University
William G. Howell,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/william-howell,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/william-g-howell,"Before coming to the University of Chicago, William taught in the government department at Harvard University and the political science department at the University of Wisconsin. In 2000, he received a PhD in political science from Stanford University.","[[('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('William', 'PERSON'), ('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('the University of Wisconsin', 'ORG')], [('2000', 'DATE'), ('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Stanford University', 'ORG')]]",Stanford University
Katherine D. Kinzler,https://psychology.uchicago.edu/directory/katherine-d-kinzler,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/katherine-d-kinzler,"Professor Kinzler joined the faculty of the University of Chicago Department of Psychology in 2008, as a Neubauer Family Assistant Professor.  She spent 2015-2019 at Cornell University, where she was most recently the Chair of the Department of Psychology. She completed her B.A. at Yale in Cognitive Science, her Ph.D. at Harvard in Psychology, and she was a Fulbright Scholar at the École Normale Supérieure in Paris. Her research has been funded by the National Institutes of Health and the John Templeton Foundation. Her work has appeared regularly in the New York Times and other media outlets, and she was named a “Young Scientist,” one of 50 scientists under age 40 recognized by the World Economic Forum.","[[('Kinzler', 'PERSON'), ('the University of Chicago Department of Psychology', 'ORG'), ('2008', 'DATE'), ('Neubauer Family', 'PERSON')], [('2015-2019', 'DATE'), ('Cornell University', 'ORG'), ('the Chair of the Department of Psychology', 'ORG')], [('B.A.', 'GPE'), ('Yale', 'ORG'), ('Ph.D.', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Harvard', 'FAC'), ('the École Normale Supérieure', 'FAC'), ('Paris', 'GPE')], [('the National Institutes of Health', 'ORG'), ('the John Templeton Foundation', 'ORG')], [('a “Young Scientist', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('50', 'CARDINAL'), ('age 40', 'DATE'), ('the World Economic Forum', 'ORG')]]",the World Economic Forum
Emilio H. Kouri,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/emilio-kourí,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/emilio-h-kouri,Harvard University,"[[('Harvard University', 'ORG')]]",Harvard University
Gabriel Lear,https://socialthought.uchicago.edu/directory/gabriel-richardson-lear,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/gabriel-lear,"Gabriel Richardson Lear (Professor of Philosophy) works on ancient Greek and Roman philosophy. Her book, Happy Lives and the Highest Good: An Essay on Aristotle's Nicomachean Ethics (Princeton, 2004), is about the relationship between morally virtuous action and theoretical contemplation in the happiest life. She is currently writing about Plato's aesthetics and about the status of beauty as an ethical concept in the work of several philosophers. She received her PhD in Philosophy from Princeton University (2001).","[[('Gabriel Richardson Lear', 'PERSON'), ('Greek', 'NORP'), ('Roman', 'NORP')], [('Aristotle', 'PERSON'), ('2004', 'DATE')], [('Plato', 'ORG')], [('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Princeton University', 'ORG'), ('2001', 'DATE')]]",Princeton University
Mark Bradley,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/mark-philip-bradley,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/mark-bradley,Harvard University,"[[('Harvard University', 'ORG')]]",Harvard University
John Mark Hansen,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/john-mark-hansen,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/john-mark-hansen,"He joined the University faculty in 1986 as Assistant Professor in Political Science and was named an Associate Professor in 1992 and a Professor in Political Science in 1994. He served as Chairman of Political Science from 1995 to 1998, when he was named Associate Provost for Education and Research. Hansen received a BA in 1981 from the University of Kansas, an MPhil in 1983, and the PhD in 1987 from Yale University.","[[('University', 'ORG'), ('1986', 'DATE'), ('1992', 'DATE'), ('1994', 'DATE')], [('1995', 'DATE'), ('1998', 'DATE'), ('Associate Provost for Education and Research', 'ORG')], [('Hansen', 'PERSON'), ('1981', 'DATE'), ('the University of Kansas', 'ORG'), ('MPhil', 'ORG'), ('1983', 'DATE'), ('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('1987', 'DATE'), ('Yale University', 'ORG')]]",Yale University
Howard C. Nusbaum,https://psychology.uchicago.edu/directory/howard-c-nusbaum,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/howard-c-nusbaum,SUNY at Buffalo,"[[('Buffalo', 'GPE')]]",University of California
Robert Vargas,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/robert-vargas-1,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/robert-vargas,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Christina Klespies,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/christina-klespies,"Christina Klespies identifies short and long term HR goals with unit leadership and oversees allocation of resources to meet priorities. In addition, she develops human resources policies and procedures to help meet strategic goals and oversees their implementation. She also ensures compliance of staff with organizational, university, and other relevant human resources policies and procedures.  She oversees hiring, orientation, performance planning, compensation, staff development, succession planning and employee labor relations, and advises/counsels supervisors and managers on federal, state and local employment laws and regulations. Klespies has over 20 years of experience in Human Resources in Higher Education. Prior to joining the University of Chicago in 2010, Klespies worked at two state universities in Ohio. She holds a BS in Human Resources Management and a Master’s degree in Psychology, with an emphasis in Organizational Development and Diversity Management. Klespies has completed doctorate level coursework and is also certified Professional in Human Resources Management through the Society of Human Resources Management (SHRM) and the Human Resources Certification Institute (HRCI).  ","[[('Christina Klespies', 'PERSON')], [], [], [], [], [('20 years', 'DATE'), ('Human Resources in Higher Education', 'ORG')], [('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2010', 'DATE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ohio', 'GPE')], [('Human Resources Management', 'ORG'), ('Organizational Development and Diversity Management', 'ORG')], [('Professional in Human Resources Management', 'ORG'), ('the Society of Human Resources Management', 'ORG'), ('the Human Resources Certification Institute', 'ORG'), ('HRCI', 'ORG')]]",HRCI
Lisa Williams,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/lisa-williams,"Christina Klespies identifies short and long term HR goals with unit leadership and oversees allocation of resources to meet priorities. In addition, she develops human resources policies and procedures to help meet strategic goals and oversees their implementation. She also ensures compliance of staff with organizational, university, and other relevant human resources policies and procedures.  She oversees hiring, orientation, performance planning, compensation, staff development, succession planning and employee labor relations, and advises/counsels supervisors and managers on federal, state and local employment laws and regulations. Klespies has over 20 years of experience in Human Resources in Higher Education. Prior to joining the University of Chicago in 2010, Klespies worked at two state universities in Ohio. She holds a BS in Human Resources Management and a Master’s degree in Psychology, with an emphasis in Organizational Development and Diversity Management. Klespies has completed doctorate level coursework and is also certified Professional in Human Resources Management through the Society of Human Resources Management (SHRM) and the Human Resources Certification Institute (HRCI).  ","[[('Christina Klespies', 'PERSON')], [], [], [], [], [('20 years', 'DATE'), ('Human Resources in Higher Education', 'ORG')], [('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2010', 'DATE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ohio', 'GPE')], [('Human Resources Management', 'ORG'), ('Organizational Development and Diversity Management', 'ORG')], [('Professional in Human Resources Management', 'ORG'), ('the Society of Human Resources Management', 'ORG'), ('the Human Resources Certification Institute', 'ORG'), ('HRCI', 'ORG')]]",HRCI
Chad  Cyrenne,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/chad-cyrenne,"Christina Klespies identifies short and long term HR goals with unit leadership and oversees allocation of resources to meet priorities. In addition, she develops human resources policies and procedures to help meet strategic goals and oversees their implementation. She also ensures compliance of staff with organizational, university, and other relevant human resources policies and procedures.  She oversees hiring, orientation, performance planning, compensation, staff development, succession planning and employee labor relations, and advises/counsels supervisors and managers on federal, state and local employment laws and regulations. Klespies has over 20 years of experience in Human Resources in Higher Education. Prior to joining the University of Chicago in 2010, Klespies worked at two state universities in Ohio. She holds a BS in Human Resources Management and a Master’s degree in Psychology, with an emphasis in Organizational Development and Diversity Management. Klespies has completed doctorate level coursework and is also certified Professional in Human Resources Management through the Society of Human Resources Management (SHRM) and the Human Resources Certification Institute (HRCI).  ","[[('Christina Klespies', 'PERSON')], [], [], [], [], [('20 years', 'DATE'), ('Human Resources in Higher Education', 'ORG')], [('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2010', 'DATE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ohio', 'GPE')], [('Human Resources Management', 'ORG'), ('Organizational Development and Diversity Management', 'ORG')], [('Professional in Human Resources Management', 'ORG'), ('the Society of Human Resources Management', 'ORG'), ('the Human Resources Certification Institute', 'ORG'), ('HRCI', 'ORG')]]",HRCI
James Evans,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/james-evans,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/james-evans,Stanford University,"[[('Stanford University', 'ORG')]]",Stanford University
Paul Staniland,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/paul-staniland,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/paul-staniland,MIT,"[[('MIT', 'ORG')]]",MIT
Cate Goebel,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/cate-goebel,Paul Staniland,"[[('Paul Staniland', 'PERSON')]]",University of California
Laura Tharsen,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/laura-tharsen,Paul Staniland,"[[('Paul Staniland', 'PERSON')]]",University of California
Anna Brailovsky,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/anna-brailovsky,Paul Staniland,"[[('Paul Staniland', 'PERSON')]]",University of California
Dean Clason,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/dean-clason,Paul Staniland,"[[('Paul Staniland', 'PERSON')]]",University of California
Shikha  Evans,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/shikha-evans,Paul Staniland,"[[('Paul Staniland', 'PERSON')]]",University of California
June  Hou,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/june-hou,Paul Staniland,"[[('Paul Staniland', 'PERSON')]]",University of California
Sarah Niemann,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/sarah-niemann,Paul Staniland,"[[('Paul Staniland', 'PERSON')]]",University of California
Michaela Appeltova,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/michaela-m%C3%AD%C5%A1a-appeltov%C3%A1,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/michaela-appeltova,"I received a PhD in History, with distinction, from the University of Chicago in 2019. I hold an MA in MAPSS from the University of Chicago (2011) and an MA in Gender Studies from the Charles University in Prague (2008).","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('History', 'GPE'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2019', 'DATE')], [('MA', 'GPE'), ('MAPSS', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2011', 'DATE'), ('MA', 'ORG'), ('the Charles University', 'ORG'), ('Prague', 'GPE'), ('2008', 'DATE')]]",the Charles University
Evelyn Atkinson,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/evelyn-atkinson,"I received a PhD in History, with distinction, from the University of Chicago in 2019. I hold an MA in MAPSS from the University of Chicago (2011) and an MA in Gender Studies from the Charles University in Prague (2008).","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('History', 'GPE'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2019', 'DATE')], [('MA', 'GPE'), ('MAPSS', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2011', 'DATE'), ('MA', 'ORG'), ('the Charles University', 'ORG'), ('Prague', 'GPE'), ('2008', 'DATE')]]",the Charles University
Zachary Barr,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/zachary-barr,"I received a PhD in History, with distinction, from the University of Chicago in 2019. I hold an MA in MAPSS from the University of Chicago (2011) and an MA in Gender Studies from the Charles University in Prague (2008).","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('History', 'GPE'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2019', 'DATE')], [('MA', 'GPE'), ('MAPSS', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2011', 'DATE'), ('MA', 'ORG'), ('the Charles University', 'ORG'), ('Prague', 'GPE'), ('2008', 'DATE')]]",the Charles University
Ingrid D. Becker,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/ingrid-d-becker,"I received a PhD in History, with distinction, from the University of Chicago in 2019. I hold an MA in MAPSS from the University of Chicago (2011) and an MA in Gender Studies from the Charles University in Prague (2008).","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('History', 'GPE'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2019', 'DATE')], [('MA', 'GPE'), ('MAPSS', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2011', 'DATE'), ('MA', 'ORG'), ('the Charles University', 'ORG'), ('Prague', 'GPE'), ('2008', 'DATE')]]",the Charles University
Emily Bock,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/emily-bock,"I received a PhD in History, with distinction, from the University of Chicago in 2019. I hold an MA in MAPSS from the University of Chicago (2011) and an MA in Gender Studies from the Charles University in Prague (2008).","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('History', 'GPE'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2019', 'DATE')], [('MA', 'GPE'), ('MAPSS', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2011', 'DATE'), ('MA', 'ORG'), ('the Charles University', 'ORG'), ('Prague', 'GPE'), ('2008', 'DATE')]]",the Charles University
Kyla Bourne,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/kyla-bourne,"I received a PhD in History, with distinction, from the University of Chicago in 2019. I hold an MA in MAPSS from the University of Chicago (2011) and an MA in Gender Studies from the Charles University in Prague (2008).","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('History', 'GPE'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2019', 'DATE')], [('MA', 'GPE'), ('MAPSS', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2011', 'DATE'), ('MA', 'ORG'), ('the Charles University', 'ORG'), ('Prague', 'GPE'), ('2008', 'DATE')]]",the Charles University
Manuel Cabal,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/manuel-cabal,"I received a PhD in History, with distinction, from the University of Chicago in 2019. I hold an MA in MAPSS from the University of Chicago (2011) and an MA in Gender Studies from the Charles University in Prague (2008).","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('History', 'GPE'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2019', 'DATE')], [('MA', 'GPE'), ('MAPSS', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2011', 'DATE'), ('MA', 'ORG'), ('the Charles University', 'ORG'), ('Prague', 'GPE'), ('2008', 'DATE')]]",the Charles University
Nick  Campbell-Seremetis,https://www.nickcs.net/,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/nick-campbell-seremetis,"Welcome! I received my PhD in political science from the University of Chicago in Summer 2020, and am a current post-doctoral fellow at the University of Notre Dame International Security Center (NDISC).","[[], [('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('Summer 2020', 'DATE'), ('the University of Notre Dame International Security Center', 'ORG'), ('NDISC', 'ORG')]]",NDISC
Carlos Cardenas-Iniguez,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/carlos-cardenas-iniguez,"Welcome! I received my PhD in political science from the University of Chicago in Summer 2020, and am a current post-doctoral fellow at the University of Notre Dame International Security Center (NDISC).","[[], [('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('Summer 2020', 'DATE'), ('the University of Notre Dame International Security Center', 'ORG'), ('NDISC', 'ORG')]]",NDISC
Wilma A. Bainbridge,https://psychology.uchicago.edu/directory/wilma-bainbridge,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/wilma-bainbridge,"Wilma A. Bainbridge is an Assistant Professor in the Department of Psychology. She received her B.A. in Cognitive Science from Yale University, studying both visual neuroscience and human-robot interaction. After a year-long research internship on robotics at the University of Tokyo, she completed her Ph.D in Brain & Cognitive Sciences at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, studying vision and memory. She then completed postdoctoral training at the National Institute of Mental Health before coming to the University of Chicago.","[[('Wilma A. Bainbridge', 'PERSON'), ('the Department of Psychology', 'ORG')], [('B.A.', 'GPE'), ('Cognitive Science', 'ORG'), ('Yale University', 'ORG')], [('year-long', 'DATE'), ('the University of Tokyo', 'ORG'), ('Brain & Cognitive Sciences', 'ORG'), ('the Massachusetts Institute of Technology', 'ORG')], [('the National Institute of Mental Health', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG')]]",the University of Chicago
Akram Bakkour,https://psychology.uchicago.edu/directory/akram-bakkour-5,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/akram-bakkour,Department of Psychology,[[]],University of California
Kathleen Belew,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/kathleen-belew,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/kathleen-belew,Yale University,"[[('Yale University', 'ORG')]]",Yale University
Lin Bian,https://psychology.uchicago.edu/directory/lin-bian,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/lin-bian,"Lin Bian is joining the Department of Psychology as an Assistant Professor in 2021. Before moving to the University of Chicago, she was the Evalyn Edwards Milman Assistant Professor at Cornell University. Lin obtained her B.S. in Psychology at Zhejiang University (China) and her Ph.D. in Developmental Psychology at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, and then completed her postdoctoral training at Stanford University.","[[('Lin Bian', 'PERSON'), ('the Department of Psychology', 'ORG'), ('2021', 'DATE')], [('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('Cornell University', 'ORG')], [('Lin', 'PERSON'), ('B.S.', 'NORP'), ('Zhejiang University (China', 'ORG'), ('the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign', 'ORG'), ('Stanford University', 'ORG')]]",Stanford University
Ruth Bloch Rubin,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/ruth-bloch-rubin,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/ruth-bloch-rubin,"Ruth Bloch Rubin studies American politics, with a substantive focus on legislative institutions, political parties, and American political development. Combining archival and interview data, her current work explores how divisions within political parties drive congressional development and structure lawmaking. Challenging existing theories of party power in Congress, she highlights the role of intraparty organizations in shaping both substantive and procedural change. Bloch Rubin is also working on a project that examines Congress’s provision of health services to American Indians in the early nineteenth century. She joins the University of Chicago from Harvard University, where she was Robert Wood Johnson Scholar in Health Policy Research. She earned her PhD in Political Science from the University of California, Berkeley in 2014.","[[('Ruth Bloch Rubin', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('American', 'NORP')], [], [('Congress', 'ORG')], [('Bloch Rubin', 'PERSON'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('American Indians', 'NORP'), ('the early nineteenth century', 'DATE')], [('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('Robert Wood Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Health Policy Research', 'ORG')], [('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the University of California, Berkeley', 'ORG'), ('2014', 'DATE')]]","the University of California, Berkeley"
Benjamin Brooks,https://economics.uchicago.edu/directory/benjamin-brooks,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/benjamin-brooks,Princeton University,"[[('Princeton University', 'ORG')]]",Princeton University
Austin Carson,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/austin-carson,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/austin-carson,"Austin Carson is an assistant professor in the Department of Political Science at the University of Chicago. His main research focus is the politics of secrecy in International Relations. His first book, Secret Wars: Covert Conflict in International Politics (Princeton UP 2018), analyzes puzzling secrecy patterns that arise when outside powers intervene in foreign wars. The book develops a theory based on conflict escalation dynamics, showing that states use covert intervention and conceal others' covert activity to keep war limited. An article analyzing the secret side of the Korean War was published in International Organization. His second book project, in collaboration with Allison Carnegie (Columbia), analyzes the role of intelligence and other forms of sensitive information in international organizations. His other research addresses the signaling value of covert action, secrecy's role in insulating international regimes from damaging rule violations, and dynamics of limited war. Dr. Carson received his PhD from Ohio State, BA from Michigan State, and has held research fellowships at Princeton University's Niehaus Center for Globalization and Governance and George Washington University's Institute for Security and Conflict Studies.","[[('Austin Carson', 'PERSON'), ('the Department of Political Science', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG')], [('International Relations', 'ORG')], [('first', 'ORDINAL')], [('2018', 'DATE')], [], [('the Korean War', 'EVENT')], [('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Allison Carnegie', 'ORG'), ('Columbia', 'ORG')], [], [('Carson', 'PERSON'), ('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Ohio State', 'ORG'), ('BA', 'ORG'), ('Michigan State', 'GPE'), (""Princeton University's"", 'ORG'), ('Niehaus Center for Globalization and Governance', 'ORG'), (""George Washington University's"", 'ORG'), ('Institute for Security and Conflict Studies', 'ORG')]]",Institute for Security and Conflict Studies
Marisa Casillas,https://humdev.uchicago.edu/directory/marisa-casillas,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/marisa-casillas,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Elizabeth Chatterjee,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/elizabeth-chatterjee,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/elizabeth-chatterjee,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Joyce Bell,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/joyce-bell,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/joyce-bell,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Marc Berman,https://psychology.uchicago.edu/directory/marc-g-berman,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/marc-berman,"Marc Berman is an Associate Professor in the Department of Psychology and is involved in the Cognition, Social and Integrative Neuroscience programs. Understanding the relationship between individual psychological and neural processing and environmental factors lies at the heart of my research. In my lab we utilize brain imaging, behavioral experimentation, computational neuroscience and statistical models to quantify the person, the environment and their interactions. Marc received his B.S.E. in Industrial and Operations Engineering (IOE) from the University of Michigan and his Ph.D. in Psychology and IOE from the University of Michigan. He received post-doctoral training at the University of Toronto's Rotman Research Institute at Baycrest. Before arriving to Chicago he was an Assistant Professor of Psychology at the University of South Carolina.","[[('Marc Berman', 'PERSON'), ('the Department of Psychology', 'ORG')], [], [], [('Marc', 'PERSON'), ('B.S.E. in', 'PRODUCT'), ('the University of Michigan', 'ORG'), ('Ph.D. in Psychology and IOE', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the University of Michigan', 'ORG')], [(""the University of Toronto's"", 'ORG'), ('Rotman Research Institute', 'ORG'), ('Baycrest', 'ORG')], [('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('the University of South Carolina', 'ORG')]]",the University of South Carolina
Dain Borges,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/dain-borges,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/dain-borges,Stanford University,"[[('Stanford University', 'ORG')]]",Stanford University
Matthew M. Briones,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/matthew-briones,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/matthew-m-briones,Harvard University,"[[('Harvard University', 'ORG')]]",Harvard University
P. Sean Brotherton,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/faculty/sean-brotherton,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/p-sean-brotherton,Gill University,"[[('Gill University', 'ORG')]]",Gill University
Rachel Lee Fulton Brown,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/rachel-fulton-brown,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/rachel-lee-fulton-brown,Columbia University,"[[('Columbia University', 'ORG')]]",Columbia University
Ralph A. Austen,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/ralph-austen,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/ralph-austen,Harvard University,"[[('Harvard University', 'ORG')]]",Harvard University
Leonard Binder,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/leonard-binder,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/leonard-binder,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Norman Bradburn,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/norman-bradburn,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Alain Bresson,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/alain-bresson,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/alain-bresson-0,University of Franche,"[[('University of Franche', 'ORG')]]",University of Franche
Robert A. Butler,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/robert-butler,University of Franche,"[[('University of Franche', 'ORG')]]",University of Franche
Maria Manuel Carneiro Da Cunha,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/emeritus-faculty/manuela-carneiro-da-cunha,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/maria-manuel-carneiro-da-cunha,University of Campinas,"[[('University of Campinas', 'ORG')]]",University of Campinas
Wendy Doniger,https://socialthought.uchicago.edu/directory/wendy-doniger,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/wendy-doniger,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Leora Auslander,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/leora-auslander,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/leora-auslander,Brown University,"[[('Brown University', 'ORG')]]",Brown University
Edward Awh,https://psychology.uchicago.edu/directory/edward-s-awh,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/edward-awh,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Stephane Bonhomme,https://economics.uchicago.edu/directory/st%C3%A9phane-bonhomme,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/stephane-bonhomme,University of Paris,"[[('University of Paris', 'ORG')]]",University of Paris
Julie Y. Chu,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/faculty/julie-chu,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/julie-y-chu,New York University,"[[('New York University', 'ORG')]]",New York University
Molly Cunningham,https://chicago.academia.edu/MollyKCunningham,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/molly-cunningham,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Natalja Czarnecki,https://voices.uchicago.edu/nataljaczarnecki/,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/natalja-czarnecki,"Natalja Czarnecki received her PhD in Anthropology from the University of Chicago in August, 2020. She is a sociocultural anthropologist specializing in processes of EU reform and border making in post-socialist contexts (Poland and Georgia). Her work is concerned with the politics of gender, the making of moral authority, public forms of trust, and the politicization of safety. Her current book project, an ethnography of public trust through the lens of regulatory authority and reform in post-Soviet Tbilisi, Georgia, focuses on everyday interactions between institutions that comprise “food safety reform” – a state bureaucracy, official and unofficial food markets, and practices of food consumers themselves. ","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('August, 2020', 'DATE')], [('EU', 'ORG'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Georgia', 'GPE')], [], [('post-Soviet', 'NORP'), ('Tbilisi', 'GPE'), ('Georgia', 'GPE')]]",EU
Suchismita Das,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/affiliates,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/suchismita-das,"(PhD, New York University, 2018; Collegiate Assistant Professor, Social Sciences) sociocultural anthropology; socialism and capitalism; Islam; materiality and semiotics; Former Soviet Union; Central Asia; Tajikistan.","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('New York University', 'ORG'), ('2018', 'DATE'), ('Social Sciences', 'ORG'), ('Islam', 'ORG'), ('Soviet Union', 'GPE'), ('Central Asia', 'LOC'), ('Tajikistan', 'GPE')]]",Islam
Shannon Dawdy,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/faculty/shannon-lee-dawdy,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/shannon-dawdy,"PhD, University of Michigan, 2003 (Anthropology and History)","[[('PhD, University of Michigan', 'ORG'), ('2003', 'DATE')]]","PhD, University of Michigan"
Michael Dietler,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/faculty/michael-dietler,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/michael-dietler,UC Berkeley,[[]],University of California
Michael A. Fisch,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/faculty/michael-fisch,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/michael-fisch,Columbia University,"[[('Columbia University', 'ORG')]]",Columbia University
Ashley Drake,https://chicago.academia.edu/AshleyDrake,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/ashley-drake,"Ashley Elizabeth Drake received herPhD in Comparative Human Development from the University of Chicago in 2020. Drake is a cultural and medical anthropologist with research interests in human-animal interaction, science and technology studies, and military studies. Her current book projectexplores how the U.S. Military develops and deploys human-animal affective relationships as biotechnological equipment in combat zones, particularly through the use of dog-handler detection teams.","[[('Ashley Elizabeth Drake', 'PERSON'), ('herPhD', 'CARDINAL'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')], [], [('U.S.', 'GPE')]]",the University of Chicago
Terra Edwards,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/terra-edwards,"Ashley Elizabeth Drake received herPhD in Comparative Human Development from the University of Chicago in 2020. Drake is a cultural and medical anthropologist with research interests in human-animal interaction, science and technology studies, and military studies. Her current book projectexplores how the U.S. Military develops and deploys human-animal affective relationships as biotechnological equipment in combat zones, particularly through the use of dog-handler detection teams.","[[('Ashley Elizabeth Drake', 'PERSON'), ('herPhD', 'CARDINAL'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')], [], [('U.S.', 'GPE')]]",the University of Chicago
Michele Friedner,https://humdev.uchicago.edu/directory/michele-friedner,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/michele-friedner,"2018    “Cross-Disability” in India? On the limits of Disability as a Category and Negotiating Impairments. With Nandini Ghosh and Deepa Palanniapan. South Asia Multidisciplinary Academic Journal (SAMAJ). Free-Standing Articles, Online since 19 April 2018, connection on 20 April 2018. http://journals.openedition.org/samaj/4516","[[('2018', 'DATE')], [('India', 'GPE')], [], [('Nandini Ghosh', 'PERSON'), ('Deepa Palanniapan', 'PERSON')], [], [('19 April 2018', 'DATE'), ('20 April 2018', 'DATE')], []]",University of California
Guanglei Hong,https://humdev.uchicago.edu/directory/guanglei-hong,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/guanglei-hong,"Guanglei Hong obtained a Master's degree in Applied Statistics and a Ph.D. in Education from the University of Michigan in 2004. She is the Inaugural Chair of the University-wide Committee on Quantitative Methods in Social, Behavioral, and Health Sciences (https://voices.uchicago.edu/qrmeth/) and a member of the Committee on Education (https://voices.uchicago.edu/coed/) at the University of Chicago. Before joining the University of Chicago faculty in July 2009, she had been an Assistant Professor in the Human Development and Applied Psychology Department in the Ontario Institute for Studies in Education of the University of Toronto (OISE/UT).","[[('Guanglei Hong', 'PERSON'), ('Applied Statistics', 'ORG'), ('Ph.D.', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the University of Michigan', 'ORG'), ('2004', 'DATE')], [('the University-wide Committee on Quantitative Methods', 'ORG'), ('Social', 'GPE'), ('Health Sciences', 'ORG'), ('the Committee on Education', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG')], [('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('July 2009', 'DATE'), ('the Human Development and Applied Psychology Department', 'ORG'), ('the Ontario Institute for Studies', 'ORG'), ('the University of Toronto', 'ORG'), ('OISE/UT', 'ORG')]]",OISE/UT
Micere Keels,https://humdev.uchicago.edu/directory/micere-keels,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/micere-keels,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Dario Maestripieri,https://humdev.uchicago.edu/directory/dario-maestripieri,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/dario-maestripieri,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Tasneem Mandviwala,https://humdev.uchicago.edu/directory/tasneem-mandviwala,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/tasneem-mandviwala,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Leonardo Bursztyn,https://economics.uchicago.edu/directory/leonardo-bursztyn,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/leonardo-bursztyn,Harvard University,"[[('Harvard University', 'ORG')]]",Harvard University
Michael Dinerstein,https://economics.uchicago.edu/directory/michael-dinerstein,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/michael-dinerstein,Stanford University,"[[('Stanford University', 'ORG')]]",Stanford University
David W. Galenson,https://economics.uchicago.edu/directory/david-galenson,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/david-w-galenson,Harvard University,"[[('Harvard University', 'ORG')]]",Harvard University
Mikhail Golosov,https://economics.uchicago.edu/directory/mikhail-golosov,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/mikhail-golosov,University of Minnesota,"[[('University of Minnesota', 'ORG')]]",University of Minnesota
Michael Greenstone,https://economics.uchicago.edu/directory/michael-greenstone,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/michael-greenstone,Princeton University,"[[('Princeton University', 'ORG')]]",Princeton University
John J. Brehm,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/john-brehm,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/john-j-brehm,D Michigan,"[[('Michigan', 'GPE')]]",University of California
Cathy Cohen,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/cathy-cohen,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/cathy-cohen,D Michigan,"[[('Michigan', 'GPE')]]",University of California
Chiara Cordelli,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/chiara-cordelli,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/chiara-cordelli,"Cordelli earned her BA in philosophy from the University of Rome “La Sapienza,” where she studied aesthetics, critical theory, and the history of political thought. During her MA at University College London, she became interested in analytic philosophy. She earned her PhD in political philosophy from UCL in 2011. Before joining Chicago in 2015, she was a postdoctoral scholar at Stanford University (2011-2013) and a tenure-track assistant professor at the University of Exeter, UK (2013-2015). She held visiting positions at the Kluge Center at the Library of Congress in D.C. (2009-2010), the Center for Human Values at Princeton (2014-2015), the Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences at Stanford (2012-2013), the Safra Center for Ethics at Harvard (2017-2018) and the LIER center at EHESS in Paris (2021-2022).","[[('Cordelli', 'ORG'), ('the University of Rome', 'ORG')], [], [('University College London', 'ORG')], [('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('UCL', 'ORG'), ('2011', 'DATE')], [('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('2015', 'DATE'), ('Stanford University', 'ORG'), ('2011-2013', 'DATE'), ('the University of Exeter', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('2013-2015', 'DATE')], [('the Kluge Center', 'FAC'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('D.C.', 'GPE'), ('2009-2010', 'DATE'), ('the Center for Human Values', 'ORG'), ('Princeton', 'GPE'), ('2014-2015', 'DATE'), ('the Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences', 'ORG'), ('Stanford', 'ORG'), ('2012-2013', 'DATE'), ('the Safra Center for Ethics', 'ORG'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('2017-2018', 'DATE'), ('LIER', 'ORG'), ('EHESS', 'ORG'), ('Paris', 'GPE'), ('2021-2022', 'DATE')]]",EHESS
Michael C. Dawson,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/michael-dawson,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/michael-c-dawson,Arthur Professor of Political,"[[('Arthur', 'PERSON')]]",University of California
Mark Deming,http://www.markdeming.net/,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/mark-deming,"I received my PhD from the University of Chicago’s Political Science Department in August 2020. Prior to my PhD studies, I completed an MA in International Relations at the University of Chicago’s Committee on International Relations.","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('Political Science Department', 'ORG'), ('August 2020', 'DATE')], [('PhD', 'ORG'), ('MA in', 'ORG'), ('International Relations', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago’s Committee on International Relations', 'ORG')]]",the University of Chicago’s Committee on International Relations
Andrew Eggers,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/andrew-eggers,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/andrew-eggers,D Harvard,"[[('Harvard', 'ORG')]]",Harvard
Jean Decety,https://psychology.uchicago.edu/directory/jean-decety,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/jean-decety,"Professor Decety received a Ph.D. in Neuroscience from the University Claude Bernard (France), and then completed a two-year postdoctoral fellowship in Sweden, at Lund University Hospital and at the Karolinska Hospital in Stockholm in the Departments of Clinical Neurophysiology and Neuroradiology.","[[('Decety', 'PERSON'), ('Ph.D.', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Neuroscience', 'ORG'), ('the University Claude Bernard', 'ORG'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('two-year', 'DATE'), ('Sweden', 'GPE'), ('Lund University Hospital', 'ORG'), ('the Karolinska Hospital', 'FAC'), ('Stockholm', 'GPE')]]",Lund University Hospital
David  Gallo,https://psychology.uchicago.edu/directory/david-gallo,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/david-gallo,"David A. Gallo joined the faculty of the University of Chicago in 2005. He received his B.A. from Wesleyan University in 1997, his Ph.D. from Washington University in St. Louis in 2002, and was an NIH-sponsored postdoctoral fellow at Harvard University until 2005. He researches the basic neurocognitive processes of human memory, how we actively (and sometimes inaccurately) reconstruct the past, and how healthy aging and Alzheimer’s disease affect these processes. For more detailed information, visit the Memory Lab Webpage (http://memorylab.uchicago.edu).","[[('David A. Gallo', 'PERSON'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2005', 'DATE')], [('B.A.', 'GPE'), ('Wesleyan University', 'ORG'), ('1997', 'DATE'), ('Ph.D.', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Washington University', 'ORG'), ('St. Louis', 'GPE'), ('2002', 'DATE'), ('NIH', 'ORG'), ('Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('2005', 'DATE')], [], []]",Harvard University
Susan Goldin-Meadow,https://psychology.uchicago.edu/directory/susan-goldin-meadow,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/susan-goldin-meadow,"Susan Goldin-Meadow is the Beardsley Ruml Distinguished Service Professor in the Department of Psychology and Committee on Human Development at the University of Chicago. A year spent at the Piagetian Institute in Geneva while an undergraduate at Smith College piqued her interest in the relationship between language and thought, interests she continued to pursue in her doctoral work at the University of Pennsylvania (Ph.D. 1975). At Penn and in collaboration with Lila Gleitman and Heidi Feldman, she began her studies exploring whether children who lack a (usable) model for language can nevertheless create a language with their hands. She has found that deaf children whose profound hearing losses prevent them from learning the speech than surrounds them, and whose hearing parents have not exposed them to sign, invent gesture systems which are structured in language-like ways. This interest in how the manual modality can serve the needs of communication and thinking led to her current work on the gestures that accompany speech in hearing individuals. She has found that gesture can convey substantive information – information that is often not expressed in the speech it accompanies. Gesture can thus reveal secrets of the mind to those who pay attention.","[[('Susan Goldin-Meadow', 'PERSON'), ('the Beardsley Ruml Distinguished Service', 'FAC'), ('the Department of Psychology and Committee on Human Development', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG')], [('A year', 'DATE'), ('the Piagetian Institute', 'ORG'), ('Geneva', 'GPE'), ('Smith College', 'ORG'), ('the University of Pennsylvania (', 'ORG'), ('1975', 'DATE')], [('Penn', 'PERSON'), ('Lila Gleitman', 'PERSON'), ('Heidi Feldman', 'PERSON')], [], [], [], []]",the University of Pennsylvania (
Leslie Kay,https://psychology.uchicago.edu/directory/leslie-m-kay,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/leslie-kay,"I received my BA in Liberal Arts from St. John's College in Santa Fe, New Mexico and then worked for the original GenBank project at Los Alamos National Laboratory from 1982-85. I worked as a programmer/analyst in business applications for a number of years in the mid- to late eighties, and then returned to graduate school at UC Berkeley. I did my dissertation research in the laboratory of Walter J. Freeman, and received my PhD in Biophysics in 1995. I did my postdoctoral research in the laboratory of Gilles Laurent at the California Institute of Technology, where I studied olfactory bulb mitral cell responses to changes in odor context. I have been at The University of Chicago since 2000, and my laboratory studies olfactory and limbic system neurophysiology, focusing on the mechanisms and functions associated with intra- and inter-regional oscillatory cooperativity.","[[('Liberal Arts', 'ORG'), (""St. John's"", 'GPE'), ('Santa Fe', 'GPE'), ('New Mexico', 'GPE'), ('GenBank', 'ORG'), ('Los Alamos National Laboratory', 'ORG'), ('1982-85', 'DATE')], [('a number of years', 'DATE'), ('UC Berkeley', 'ORG')], [('Walter J. Freeman', 'PERSON'), ('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Biophysics', 'GPE'), ('1995', 'DATE')], [('Gilles Laurent', 'ORG'), ('the California Institute of Technology', 'ORG')], [('The University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('2000', 'DATE')]]",The University of Chicago
David Gutherz,https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/www.npr.org/podcasts/510307/invisibilia__;!!BpyFHLRN4TMTrA!qaO0rCiKUcovPSEj74NlIF1AAzHyTiS41FNx4hAOCT99mhG0JQqUA1MhYcbM55lmzA$,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/david-gutherz,"David Max Gutherz was born on Kibbutz Gezer and spent most of his youth in Lynchburg, Virginia. After studying the philosophy of religion at Oberlin College, David received his MA and PhD at the Committee on Social Thought. He is interested in historicizing the cultural, scientific, and affective practices that make authoritarianism seem reasonable and is currently working on a book entitled, The Great Unbinding: Fascism and the Italian Origins of a Global New Left, which is based on the dissertation he submitted in 2019. In addition to publishing scholarly essays, David has also collaborated on a number of podcasts, mostly for NPR's Invisibilia and the New Books Network, and translated works by Ernesto de Martino, Elvio Fachinelli, and the DEMAU collective.","[[('David Max Gutherz', 'PERSON'), ('Kibbutz Gezer', 'PERSON'), ('Lynchburg', 'GPE'), ('Virginia', 'GPE')], [('Oberlin College', 'ORG'), ('David', 'PERSON'), ('MA', 'PERSON'), ('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the Committee on Social Thought', 'ORG')], [('Italian', 'NORP'), ('2019', 'DATE')], [('David', 'PERSON'), ('NPR', 'ORG'), ('Invisibilia', 'ORG'), ('the New Books Network', 'ORG'), ('Ernesto de Martino', 'PERSON'), ('Elvio Fachinelli', 'PERSON'), ('DEMAU', 'ORG')]]",DEMAU
Joel Isaac,https://socialthought.uchicago.edu/directory/joel-isaac,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/joel-isaac,"I am an historian of modern social and political thought.  I focus in particular on American and British traditions of social thought. My earliest research examined how theories of knowledge drove important changes in the human sciences during the twentieth century. Much of this work found its way into my first book, Working Knowledge: Making the Human Sciences from Parsons to Kuhn (Cambridge, MA: Harvard University Press, 2012), which was awarded the Gladstone Prize by the Royal Historical Society, UK.","[[], [('American', 'NORP'), ('British', 'NORP')], [('the twentieth century', 'DATE')], [('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Working Knowledge: Making the Human Sciences from Parsons to Kuhn (Cambridge', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Harvard University Press', 'ORG'), ('2012', 'DATE'), ('the Gladstone Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the Royal Historical Society', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE')]]",the Royal Historical Society
Benjamin Jeffery,http://www.wordofbenjeffery.com/,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/benjamin-jeffery,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Jonathan Lear,https://socialthought.uchicago.edu/directory/jonathan-lear,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/jonathan-lear,"Jonathan Lear is the John U. Nef Distinguished Service Professor at the Committee on Social Thought and in the Department of Philosophy. His work focuses on the philosophical understanding of the human psyche—and the ethical implications that flow from us being the kind of creatures we are. He trained in Philosophy at Cambridge University and The Rockefeller University where he received his PhD in 1978. He works primarily on philosophical conceptions of the human psyche from Socrates to the present. He also trained as a psychoanalyst at the Western New England Institute for Psychoanalysis. His books include: Radical Hope: Ethics in the Face of Cultural Devastation (2006); Aristotle and Logical Theory (1980); Aristotle: The Desire to Understand (1988); Love and Its Place in Nature: A Philosophical Interpretation of Freudian Psychoanalysis (1990); Open Minded: Working out the Logic of the Soul (1998); Happiness, Death and the Remainder of Life (2000); Therapeutic Action: An Earnest Plea for Irony (2003); A Case for Irony (2011); and Freud (2015); His most recent book is Wisdom Won From Illness: Essays in Philosophy and Psychoanalysis (Harvard University Press, 2017). He is a recipient of the Andrew W. Mellon Foundation Distinguished Achievement Award. In 2014, he was appointed the Roman Family Director of the Neubauer Collegium for Culture and Society and continues in that role currently. He is a Fellow of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences and a member of the American Philosophical Society.","[[('Jonathan Lear', 'PERSON'), ('the Committee on Social Thought', 'ORG'), ('the Department of Philosophy', 'ORG')], [], [('Cambridge University', 'ORG'), ('The Rockefeller University', 'ORG'), ('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('1978', 'DATE')], [('Socrates', 'ORG')], [('the Western New England Institute for Psychoanalysis', 'ORG')], [('2006', 'DATE'), ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'), ('1980', 'DATE')], [('1988', 'DATE')], [('1990', 'DATE')], [], [('1998', 'DATE'), ('2000', 'DATE'), ('2003', 'DATE'), ('2011', 'DATE'), ('Freud', 'PERSON'), ('2015', 'DATE'), ('Wisdom Won From Illness: Essays in Philosophy and Psychoanalysis', 'ORG'), ('Harvard University Press', 'ORG'), ('2017', 'DATE')], [('the Andrew W. Mellon Foundation', 'ORG')], [('2014', 'DATE'), ('Roman', 'NORP'), ('the Neubauer Collegium for Culture and Society', 'ORG')], [('the American Academy of Arts and Sciences', 'ORG'), ('the American Philosophical Society', 'ORG')]]",the American Philosophical Society
Eliza Little,https://socialthought.uchicago.edu/directory/eliza-starbuck-little,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/eliza-little,"In 2020-1, Eliza Starbuck Little is a Postdoctoral Teaching Fellow in the Division of Social Sciences and The Committee on Social Thought. She received her PhD from Social Thought in 2020, with a specialization in philosophy.","[[('2020-1', 'DATE'), ('Eliza Starbuck Little', 'ORG'), ('the Division of Social Sciences', 'ORG'), ('The Committee on Social Thought', 'ORG')], [('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Social Thought', 'ORG'), ('2020', 'DATE')]]",Social Thought
David Nirenberg,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/david-nirenberg,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/david-nirenberg,Princeton University,"[[('Princeton University', 'ORG')]]",Princeton University
Thomas Pavel,https://socialthought.uchicago.edu/directory/thomas-pavel,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/thomas-pavel,"Fictional Worlds, Cambridge, MA: Harvard University Press, 1986.  French translation, Univers de la fiction, Paris: Editions du Seuil, coll. ""Poétique"", 1988.  Italian edition, Milan: Einaudi, 1992, Romanian translation, Bucarest, 1994, Spanish translation, Caracas, 1996.","[[('Cambridge', 'GPE'), ('MA', 'GPE'), ('Harvard University Press', 'ORG'), ('1986', 'DATE')], [('French', 'NORP'), ('Paris', 'GPE')], [('Poétique', 'PERSON'), ('1988', 'DATE')], [('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Milan', 'GPE'), ('Einaudi, 1992', 'DATE'), ('Romanian', 'NORP'), ('Bucarest', 'ORG'), ('1994', 'DATE'), ('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('Caracas', 'GPE'), ('1996', 'DATE')]]",Bucarest
Mark Payne,https://socialthought.uchicago.edu/directory/mark-payne,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/mark-payne,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Robert B. Pippin,https://socialthought.uchicago.edu/directory/robert-b-pippin,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/robert-b-pippin,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Neil Brenner,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/neil-brenner,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/neil-brenner,University of Chicago,"[[('University of Chicago', 'ORG')]]",University of Chicago
Terry N. Clark,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/terry-n-clark,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/terry-n-clark,Columbia University,"[[('Columbia University', 'ORG')]]",Columbia University
Elisabeth S. Clemens,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/elisabeth-s-clemens,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/elisabeth-s-clemens,University of Chicago,"[[('University of Chicago', 'ORG')]]",University of Chicago
Rene Flores,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/ren%C3%A9-d-flores,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/rene-flores,Princeton University,"[[('Princeton University', 'ORG')]]",Princeton University
Rachel Glennerster,https://rglennerster.ssd.uchicago.edu/,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/rachel-glennerster,"Glennerster helped establish Deworm the World, which has helped deworm 23 million children worldwide. She previously worked at the IMF and Her Majesty's Treasury. She has a PhD in Economics from Birkbeck College, University of London, and is coauthor of Strong Medicine: Creating Incentives for Pharmaceutical Research on Neglected Diseases and Running Randomized Evaluations: A Practical Guide.","[[('Deworm the World', 'ORG'), ('23 million', 'CARDINAL')], [('Treasury', 'ORG')], [('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Birkbeck College, University of London', 'ORG')]]","Birkbeck College, University of London"
Gary B. Herrigel,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/gary-herrigel,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/gary-b-herrigel,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Emily Talen,https://urbanism.uchicago.edu/,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/emily-talen,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Robert  Dreeben,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/robert-dreeben,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Irene Elkin,https://ssa.uchicago.edu/irene-elkin,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/irene-elkin,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Edgar G. Epps,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/edgar-g-epps,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Emily Osborn,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/emily-lynn-osborn,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/emily-osborn,Stanford University,"[[('Stanford University', 'ORG')]]",Stanford University
Paul Poast,https://voices.uchicago.edu/socscisummermethods,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/paul-poast,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Brodwyn M. Fischer,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/brodwyn-fischer,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/brodwyn-m-fischer,Harvard University,"[[('Harvard University', 'ORG')]]",Harvard University
James Heckman,https://economics.uchicago.edu/directory/james-j-heckman,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/james-heckman,Princeton University,"[[('Princeton University', 'ORG')]]",Princeton University
Alan  Kolata,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/faculty/alan-kolata,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/alan-kolata,"(PhD, Harvard, 1978) Bernard E. and Ellen C. Sunny Distinguished Service Professor of Anthropology and of Social Sciences in the College","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('1978', 'DATE')], [('Bernard E.', 'PERSON'), ('Ellen C.', 'PERSON')], [('Social Sciences', 'ORG')]]",Social Sciences
Stephan Palmié,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/faculty/stephan-palmie,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/stephan-palmie,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Thomas Holt,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/thomas-c-holt,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/thomas-holt,Yale University,"[[('Yale University', 'ORG')]]",Yale University
Amy Dru Stanley,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/amy-dru-stanley,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/amy-dru-stanley,Yale University,"[[('Yale University', 'ORG')]]",Yale University
Lisa Wedeen,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/lisa-wedeen,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/lisa-wedeen,D California,"[[('California', 'GPE')]]",University of California
Deirdre Lyons,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/deirdre-lyons,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/deirdre-lyons,"Dr. Deirdre Lyons is a historian working on slavery and its afterlives in the Caribbean. Specializing in the French Antilles, her work examines how gender, race, and family shaped slavery, abolition, and emancipation over the course of the nineteenth century. Drawing on two years of archival research in France, Martinique, and Guadeloupe, her current book project analyzes slavery and abolition in the French Antilles. Dr. Lyons received her PhD in History from the University of Chicago, where she continues to teach courses that familiarize students with critical race and gender studies, the history of colonization and decolonization in the Atlantic world, slavery and its afterlives in the Americas, and social theory. She is currently working on her manuscript and preparing an article on enslaved women’s freedom suits in early-nineteenth-century Martinique and Guadeloupe.","[[('Deirdre Lyons', 'PERSON'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC')], [('French', 'NORP'), ('Antilles', 'PRODUCT'), ('the nineteenth century', 'DATE')], [('two years', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Martinique', 'GPE'), ('Guadeloupe', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Antilles', 'PRODUCT')], [('Lyons', 'PERSON'), ('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('History', 'GPE'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('Atlantic', 'LOC'), ('Americas', 'LOC')], [('Martinique', 'GPE'), ('Guadeloupe', 'GPE')]]",the University of Chicago
Victoria Nguyen,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/victoria-nguyen,"Dr. Deirdre Lyons is a historian working on slavery and its afterlives in the Caribbean. Specializing in the French Antilles, her work examines how gender, race, and family shaped slavery, abolition, and emancipation over the course of the nineteenth century. Drawing on two years of archival research in France, Martinique, and Guadeloupe, her current book project analyzes slavery and abolition in the French Antilles. Dr. Lyons received her PhD in History from the University of Chicago, where she continues to teach courses that familiarize students with critical race and gender studies, the history of colonization and decolonization in the Atlantic world, slavery and its afterlives in the Americas, and social theory. She is currently working on her manuscript and preparing an article on enslaved women’s freedom suits in early-nineteenth-century Martinique and Guadeloupe.","[[('Deirdre Lyons', 'PERSON'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC')], [('French', 'NORP'), ('Antilles', 'PRODUCT'), ('the nineteenth century', 'DATE')], [('two years', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Martinique', 'GPE'), ('Guadeloupe', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Antilles', 'PRODUCT')], [('Lyons', 'PERSON'), ('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('History', 'GPE'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('Atlantic', 'LOC'), ('Americas', 'LOC')], [('Martinique', 'GPE'), ('Guadeloupe', 'GPE')]]",the University of Chicago
Omar M. McRoberts,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/omar-mcroberts,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/omar-m-mcroberts,Harvard University,"[[('Harvard University', 'ORG')]]",Harvard University
Karin Knorr Cetina,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/karin-knorr-cetina,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/karin-knorr-cetina,University of Vienna,"[[('University of Vienna', 'ORG')]]",University of Vienna
Parysa Mostajir,https://voices.uchicago.edu/pmostajir/,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/parysa-mostajir,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Salikoko Mufwene,https://chss.uchicago.edu/directory/salikoko-s-mufwene,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/salikoko-mufwene-0,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Robert J. Richards,https://chss.uchicago.edu/directory/robert-j-richards,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/robert-j-richards,"""Nature is the Poetry of Mind, or How Schelling Solved Goethe's Kantian Problems."" In Kant and the Sciences, edited by Michael Friedman and Alfred Nordman. Cambridge, MA: MIT Press, 2005.","[[('Nature is the Poetry of Mind', 'WORK_OF_ART')], [('Kant', 'PERSON'), ('Sciences', 'ORG'), ('Michael Friedman', 'PERSON'), ('Alfred Nordman', 'PERSON')], [('Cambridge', 'GPE'), ('MA', 'GPE'), ('MIT Press', 'ORG'), ('2005', 'DATE')]]",MIT Press
James T. Sparrow,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/james-t-sparrow,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/james-t-sparrow,Brown University,"[[('Brown University', 'ORG')]]",Brown University
Stephen Stigler,https://chss.uchicago.edu/directory/stephen-stigler,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/stephen-stigler,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Susan C. Levine,https://psychology.uchicago.edu/directory/susan-c-levine,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/susan-c-levine,"Susan Levine received her B.A. with honors from Simmons College in 1972, majoring in Psychology, Mathematics and Education and her Ph.D. in Psychology from M.I.T. in 1976. She joined the faculty at the University of Chicago that year. Professor Levine is the director of the UChicago Science of Learning Center.","[[('Susan Levine', 'PERSON'), ('B.A.', 'GPE'), ('Simmons College', 'ORG'), ('1972', 'DATE'), ('Ph.D. in Psychology', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('M.I.T.', 'ORG'), ('1976', 'DATE')], [('the University of Chicago', 'ORG')], [('Levine', 'PERSON'), ('the UChicago Science of Learning Center', 'ORG')]]",the UChicago Science of Learning Center
John List,https://economics.uchicago.edu/directory/john-list,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/john-list,University of Wyoming,"[[('University of Wyoming', 'ORG')]]",University of Wyoming
Derek A. Neal,https://economics.uchicago.edu/directory/derek-neal,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/derek-neal,University of Virginia,"[[('University of Virginia', 'ORG')]]",University of Virginia
Stephen Raudenbush,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/stephen-raudenbush,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/stephen-raudenbush,"B.A. Harvard University, 1968
	Ed.M. Harvard University, 1980
	Ed.D. Harvard University, 1984","[[('B.A. Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('1968', 'DATE')], [('Ed', 'PERSON'), ('M. Harvard University', 'ORG'), ('1980', 'DATE')], [('Ed', 'PERSON'), ('Harvard University', 'ORG')]]",Harvard University
Margaret B. Spencer,https://humdev.uchicago.edu/directory/margaret-beale-spencer,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/margaret-b-spencer,"I earned my PhD from the Committee on Human Development (currently the Department of Comparative Human Development) in the Child and Developmental Psychology Program. Before returning to Chicago, I was the endowed Board of Overseers Professor and Director of the Interdisciplinary Studies of Human Development (ISHD) program and faculty member in the Graduate School of Education at the University of Pennsylvania. At UPenn, I was Director of the University of Pennsylvania's Center for Health Achievement Neighborhoods Growth and Ethnic Studies (CHANGES) and also guided as its inaugural director, the W. E. B. Du Bois Collective Research Institute. Both appointments continue to frame my developmental scholarship and application of phenomenological variant of ecological systems theory (PVEST). It is a systems theory and, most important, is inclusive of all human experience and provides an identity-focused cultural ecological perspective. I evolved the theory over a decade because non-problematizing perspectives about people of color were generally unavailable.  Accordingly, P-VEST affords an authentic representation of human development processes both for Whites and People of Color as lives evolve in an ethnically, racially and economically diverse world. The conceptual framework addresses resiliency, identity, and competence formation processes for diverse humans—particularly youth—both in the United States and abroad.  ","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the Committee on Human Development', 'ORG'), ('the Department of Comparative Human Development', 'ORG'), ('the Child and Developmental Psychology Program', 'ORG')], [('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('Board of Overseers Professor', 'ORG'), ('the Interdisciplinary Studies of Human Development', 'ORG'), ('ISHD', 'ORG'), ('the Graduate School of Education', 'ORG'), ('the University of Pennsylvania', 'ORG')], [('UPenn', 'GPE'), (""the University of Pennsylvania's"", 'ORG'), ('Center for Health Achievement Neighborhoods Growth and Ethnic Studies', 'ORG'), ('W. E. B. Du Bois', 'PERSON')], [], [], [('a decade', 'DATE')], [], [], [('the United States', 'GPE')]]",Center for Health Achievement Neighborhoods Growth and Ethnic Studies
Gentry Jenkins,https://voices.uchicago.edu/gentryjenkins/,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/gentry-jenkins,"I am a Teaching Fellow in the Committee on International Relations. I received my Ph.D. in Political Science from the University of Chicago in August 2020. My research interests involve international security and comparative politics and are currently centered on the connections between state-building and armed conflict with an emphasis on revolutionary regimes. My dissertation examines the conditions under which revolutionary state projects of centralization and social transformation trigger rebellions among ethnic groups and peasant communities in peripheral territories.  In addition to my doctoral studies, I have worked as a graduate research associate for the Chicago Project on Security and Threats, where I conducted research on the targeting strategies employed by militant groups. I also served for two years as the student coordinator for the Program on International Security Policy. I hold an M.A. in International Relations from the University of Chicago’s Committee on International Relations and a B.A. in History from the University of Idaho.","[[('a Teaching Fellow', 'PERSON'), ('the Committee on International Relations', 'ORG')], [('Ph.D.', 'FAC'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('August 2020', 'DATE')], [], [], [('the Chicago Project on Security and Threats', 'ORG')], [('two years', 'DATE'), ('the Program on International Security Policy', 'ORG')], [('M.A.', 'GPE'), ('the University of Chicago’s Committee on International Relations', 'ORG'), ('B.A.', 'GPE'), ('History', 'GPE'), ('the University of Idaho', 'ORG')]]",the University of Idaho
Steven Durlauf,https://harris.uchicago.edu/directory/steven-durlauf,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/steven-durlauf,"Durlauf received a BA in economics from Harvard in 1980 where he was elected to Phi Beta Kappa and a Ph.D. in economics from Yale in 1986. He is a Fellow of the Econometric Society, Fellow of the Society for the Advancement of Economic Theory and a Research Associate of the National Bureau of Economic Research. In 2011, he was elected to the American Academy of Arts and Sciences. He is co-director of the Human Capital and Economic Opportunity Working Group, an international research network linking scholars across disciplines in the study of inequality and the sources of human flourishing and destitution. Durlauf is the current Editor of the Journal of Economic Literature.","[[('Harvard', 'ORG'), ('1980', 'DATE'), ('Phi Beta Kappa', 'ORG'), ('Ph.D.', 'FAC'), ('Yale', 'ORG'), ('1986', 'DATE')], [('the Econometric Society', 'ORG'), ('the National Bureau of Economic Research', 'ORG')], [('2011', 'DATE'), ('the American Academy of Arts and Sciences', 'ORG')], [('the Human Capital and Economic Opportunity Working Group', 'ORG')], [('the Journal of Economic Literature', 'ORG')]]",the Journal of Economic Literature
Ross M. Stolzenberg,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/ross-m-stolzenberg,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/ross-m-stolzenberg,University of Michigan,"[[('University of Michigan', 'ORG')]]",University of Michigan
Kazuo Yamaguchi,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/kazuo-yamaguchi,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/kazuo-yamaguchi,University of Chicago,"[[('University of Chicago', 'ORG')]]",University of Chicago
Ryan Jobson,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/faculty/ryan-jobson,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/ryan-jobson,Yale University,"[[('Yale University', 'ORG')]]",Yale University
John Kelly,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/faculty/john-d-kelly,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/john-kelly,University of Chicago,"[[('University of Chicago', 'ORG')]]",University of Chicago
Jill M. Mateo,https://humdev.uchicago.edu/directory/jill-mateo,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/jill-m-mateo,"Professor Mateo is an Associate Professor, as well as the Committee on Evolutionary Biology, the Institute for Mind and Biology and the College. She received her doctorate in the field of Biopsychology, Evolution of Animal Behavior from the University of Michigan in 1995. Dr. Mateo was a Research Associate with the Department of Psychology at Cornell University (1996-2002).","[[('Mateo', 'PERSON'), ('the Committee on Evolutionary Biology', 'ORG'), ('the Institute for Mind and Biology', 'ORG'), ('the College', 'ORG')], [('the University of Michigan', 'ORG'), ('1995', 'DATE')], [('Mateo', 'PERSON'), ('the Department of Psychology at Cornell University', 'ORG'), ('1996-2002', 'DATE')]]",the Department of Psychology at Cornell University
Eugene A. Raikhel,https://humdev.uchicago.edu/directory/eugene-raikhel,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/eugene-raikhel,Still Working on This,[[]],University of California
Scott Gehlbach,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/scott-gehlbach,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/scott-gehlbach,"Prior to coming to Chicago, Gehlbach was faculty at the University of Wisconsin–Madison for sixteen years. He has at various times been affiliated with both the New Economic School and the Higher School of Economics in Moscow. For the 2019–20 academic year, he is Visiting Professor, Economics Department, Sciences Po. His work has been supported by the National Science Foundation, two Fulbright-Hays Fellowships, and many other grants. He has been honored for his scholarship through numerous awards, including most recently the Michael Wallerstein Award for best article in political economy. Among other service to the profession, he is an associate editor of the Quarterly Journal of Political Science and organizer of the annual Summer Workshop in the Economic History and Historical Political Economy of Russia. Gehlbach received his PhD in political science and economics from the University of California–Berkeley.","[[('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('Gehlbach', 'GPE'), ('the University of Wisconsin', 'ORG'), ('Madison', 'PERSON'), ('sixteen years', 'DATE')], [('the New Economic School', 'ORG'), ('the Higher School of Economics', 'ORG'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')], [('the 2019–20 academic year', 'DATE'), ('Visiting Professor, Economics Department', 'ORG'), ('Sciences Po', 'PERSON')], [('the National Science Foundation', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')], [('Michael Wallerstein Award', 'PERSON')], [('the Quarterly Journal of Political Science', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')], [('Gehlbach', 'GPE'), ('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the University of California–Berkeley', 'ORG')]]",the University of California–Berkeley
Adom Getachew,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/adom-getachew,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/adom-getachew,"Adom Getachew is Neubauer Family Assistant Professor of Political Science and the College at the University of Chicago. She is a political theorist with research interests in the history of political thought, theories of race and empire, and postcolonial political theory. Her work focuses on the intellectual and political histories of Africa and the Caribbean. Her first book, Worldmaking After Empire: The Rise and Fall of Self-Determination, reconstructs an account of self-determination offered in the political thought of Black Atlantic anticolonial nationalists during the height of decolonization in the twentieth century. Adom holds a joint PhD in Political Science and African-American Studies from Yale University. She is on the faculty board of the Pozen Center for Human Rights, a fellow at the Chicago Center for Contemporary Theory, and a faculty affiliate at the Center for the Study of Race, Politics and Culture.","[[('Neubauer Family', 'PERSON'), ('the College at the University of Chicago', 'ORG')], [], [('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC')], [('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Worldmaking After Empire: The Rise and Fall of Self-Determination', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Black Atlantic', 'LOC'), ('the twentieth century', 'DATE')], [('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('Yale University', 'ORG')], [('the Pozen Center for Human\xa0Rights', 'ORG'), ('the Chicago Center for Contemporary Theory', 'ORG'), ('the Center for the Study of Race, Politics and Culture', 'ORG')]]","the Center for the Study of Race, Politics and Culture"
Jennifer Pitts,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/jennifer-pitts,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/jennifer-pitts,D Harvard,"[[('Harvard', 'ORG')]]",Harvard
Andrei Pop,https://socialthought.uchicago.edu/directory/andrei-pop,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/andrei-pop,"Andrei Pop (B.A. Stanford, Ph.D. Harvard, Art History) has published a book entitled Antiquity, Theatre, and the Painting of Henry Fuseli (Oxford, 2015) on the romantic painter and writer Henry Fuseli, a translation of Karl Rosenkranz’s 1853 Aesthetics of Ugliness, and an edited volume on the history and theory of ugliness. His second monograph, A Forest of Symbols, concerns pictures as logical objects linking fantasy and fiction to activities like formulating and testing hypotheses, particularly during the late nineteenth century revolt against empiricism in art and mathematics. The symbol, understood both sensuously and conceptually, proved a focal point for investigating how the means of representation make possible a shared world of reasons and, what is more difficult, experiences. In the same vein, Pop is interested in the relation of art and science, in dramatic and narrative art (particularly in the classical tradition), and in how modernity deals with the past. These interests intersect with others in the logic of fiction, art historiography, cartoons, comics and caricatures, popular music and science fiction, beauty and ugliness. In short, Pop studies various aspects of the nature of art and what role it plays in the good life and the bad. ","[[('Ph.D. Harvard', 'ORG'), ('Art History', 'PERSON'), ('Antiquity', 'NORP'), ('Theatre', 'GPE'), ('the Painting of Henry Fuseli\xa0', 'ORG'), ('2015', 'DATE'), ('Henry Fuseli', 'PERSON'), ('Karl Rosenkranz’s', 'PERSON'), ('1853', 'DATE'), ('Aesthetics of Ugliness', 'ORG')], [('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('A Forest of Symbols', 'ORG'), ('the late nineteenth century', 'DATE')], [], [], [], [], []]",A Forest of Symbols
Nathan Tarcov,https://political-science.uchicago.edu/directory/nathan-tarcov,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/nathan-tarcov,D Harvard,"[[('Harvard', 'ORG')]]",Harvard
Marco Garrido,https://sociology.uchicago.edu/directory/marco-garrido,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/marco-garrido,University of Michigan,"[[('University of Michigan', 'ORG')]]",University of Michigan
Mennatallah Khalil,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/graduate-students,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/mennatallah-khalil,"Dr. Mennatallah Hassan Khalil is an anthropologist working on global militarization, the underlying assumption of military power as a precursor to modernization, and the logics of militarism in our world today. A scholar of the MENA region, she studies the intersection of seemingly secular and rational institutions of power with sacred traditions and practices in contemporary Egypt, attending to military authority’s relationship to the state, family, and civil society. Menna received her PhD from University of Chicago where she taught courses in the College, Anthropology, and Divinity School. She is currently appointed in the Self Core and Anthropology Department’s tracks on Neoliberalism, Historical Imagination, Postcoloniality, and Politics. Combining analytic and comparative methods, Menna teaches students to apply canonical texts while learning about past processes and problems of modernization, racialization, and colonization as fundamental to our everyday lives, intellectual histories, and present-day debates. Her current book analyzes militarization in Egypt since World War II through the rise of national security infrastructures, and its impact on civilian lives and political imaginations. Menna's new project focuses on the War on Terror’s transformation of local-global military relations and its reorientation of Egyptian personnel’s work ethic, sense of personhood, and individual worldview of military authority.","[[('Mennatallah Hassan Khalil', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE')], [('MENA', 'ORG'), ('Egypt', 'GPE')], [], [('Menna', 'PERSON'), ('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('the College, Anthropology', 'ORG'), ('Divinity School', 'ORG')], [('the Self Core and Anthropology Department', 'ORG')], [('Neoliberalism, Historical Imagination', 'ORG'), ('Politics', 'NORP')], [('Menna', 'PERSON')], [('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('World War II', 'EVENT')], [('Menna', 'PERSON'), ('the War on Terror', 'EVENT'), ('Egyptian', 'NORP')]]","Neoliberalism, Historical Imagination"
Patrick Lewis,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/patrick-lewis,"Dr. Mennatallah Hassan Khalil is an anthropologist working on global militarization, the underlying assumption of military power as a precursor to modernization, and the logics of militarism in our world today. A scholar of the MENA region, she studies the intersection of seemingly secular and rational institutions of power with sacred traditions and practices in contemporary Egypt, attending to military authority’s relationship to the state, family, and civil society. Menna received her PhD from University of Chicago where she taught courses in the College, Anthropology, and Divinity School. She is currently appointed in the Self Core and Anthropology Department’s tracks on Neoliberalism, Historical Imagination, Postcoloniality, and Politics. Combining analytic and comparative methods, Menna teaches students to apply canonical texts while learning about past processes and problems of modernization, racialization, and colonization as fundamental to our everyday lives, intellectual histories, and present-day debates. Her current book analyzes militarization in Egypt since World War II through the rise of national security infrastructures, and its impact on civilian lives and political imaginations. Menna's new project focuses on the War on Terror’s transformation of local-global military relations and its reorientation of Egyptian personnel’s work ethic, sense of personhood, and individual worldview of military authority.","[[('Mennatallah Hassan Khalil', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE')], [('MENA', 'ORG'), ('Egypt', 'GPE')], [], [('Menna', 'PERSON'), ('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('the College, Anthropology', 'ORG'), ('Divinity School', 'ORG')], [('the Self Core and Anthropology Department', 'ORG')], [('Neoliberalism, Historical Imagination', 'ORG'), ('Politics', 'NORP')], [('Menna', 'PERSON')], [('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('World War II', 'EVENT')], [('Menna', 'PERSON'), ('the War on Terror', 'EVENT'), ('Egyptian', 'NORP')]]","Neoliberalism, Historical Imagination"
K. Bryce Lowry,https://www.nomadsciencemongolia.com/,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/k-bryce-lowry,"NOMAD Science: Northern Mongolia Adventure and Discovery in Science is a registered 501(c)3 non-profit organization that organizes international, interdisciplinary research programs based in the remote, but stunningly beautiful Darkhad Depression, northern Mongolia.","[[('Science', 'GPE'), ('501(c)3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Darkhad Depression', 'PERSON'), ('Mongolia', 'GPE')]]",University of California
Erin  McFee,https://erinmcfee.com/,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/erin-mcfee,"Erin K. McFee, Ph.D., is an anthropologist and Fulbright Scholar. She received her doctorate from the Department of Comparative Human Development at the University of Chicago and conducts field work in Colombia and Mexico on former members of non-state armed groups, trust-building,interventions, and bureaucracy. Her most recent co-edited volume,Ex-combatants and the Peace Accord with the FARC in Colombia: An Early Balance (Spanish),presents an interdisciplinary investigation into the first year of implementation of the reintegration component of the 2016 Peace Accord in Colombia. She is currently a Social Sciences Postdoctoral Teaching Fellow at The University of Chicago, and developing her dissertation into a book manuscript titledTrust after Betrayal: Social Life in the Aftermath of Atrocity.","[[('Erin K. McFee', 'PERSON'), ('Ph.D.', 'GPE')], [('the Department of Comparative Human Development', 'ORG'), ('the University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')], [('FARC', 'ORG'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('the first year', 'DATE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')], [('Social Sciences Postdoctoral Teaching Fellow', 'ORG'), ('The University of Chicago', 'ORG'), ('Betrayal', 'ORG')]]",Betrayal
Sayantan Saha Roy,https://anthropology.uchicago.edu/people/affiliates,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/sayantan-saha-roy,"(PhD, New York University, 2018; Collegiate Assistant Professor, Social Sciences) sociocultural anthropology; socialism and capitalism; Islam; materiality and semiotics; Former Soviet Union; Central Asia; Tajikistan.","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('New York University', 'ORG'), ('2018', 'DATE'), ('Social Sciences', 'ORG'), ('Islam', 'ORG'), ('Soviet Union', 'GPE'), ('Central Asia', 'LOC'), ('Tajikistan', 'GPE')]]",Islam
Kristina Pagel,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/kristina-pagel,"(PhD, New York University, 2018; Collegiate Assistant Professor, Social Sciences) sociocultural anthropology; socialism and capitalism; Islam; materiality and semiotics; Former Soviet Union; Central Asia; Tajikistan.","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('New York University', 'ORG'), ('2018', 'DATE'), ('Social Sciences', 'ORG'), ('Islam', 'ORG'), ('Soviet Union', 'GPE'), ('Central Asia', 'LOC'), ('Tajikistan', 'GPE')]]",Islam
Kelsey Robbins,No Link,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/kelsey-robbins,"(PhD, New York University, 2018; Collegiate Assistant Professor, Social Sciences) sociocultural anthropology; socialism and capitalism; Islam; materiality and semiotics; Former Soviet Union; Central Asia; Tajikistan.","[[('PhD', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('New York University', 'ORG'), ('2018', 'DATE'), ('Social Sciences', 'ORG'), ('Islam', 'ORG'), ('Soviet Union', 'GPE'), ('Central Asia', 'LOC'), ('Tajikistan', 'GPE')]]",Islam
Amy Coombs,https://history.uchicago.edu/directory/amy-coombs,https://socialsciences.uchicago.edu/directory/amy-coombs,"Amy Coombs focuses on economic history and agriculture. Prior to completing a PhD in eighteenth century British history at The University of Chicago, she earned an MS in Forestry and Natural Resources at Purdue. Her work bridges archival methods, data mining, GIS, and science writing. Her editorial features have appeared in Nature Biotechnology, the American Geophysical Union EoS, The Scientist Magazine, and other outlets. She is currently working on her first book to revise her dissertation work focusing on eighteenth century oilseed economies.
